<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome on CJUG</title><link>https://cjug.org/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome on CJUG</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://cjug.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://cjug.org/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cjug.org/about/</guid><description>About CJUG The Chicago Java User’s Group is here to help the Java Professional. We want to make Chicago the ‘best’ place to be a Java developer, by offering a support network that allows each individual Java developer to grow! Its only purpose it to serve its community by focusing in three areas:
Learning about the Java Craft Java is a very expansive language, with new innovations coming out the door every other day, and more refined techniques being contributed by the community non-stop.</description></item><item><title>Events</title><link>https://cjug.org/events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cjug.org/events/</guid><description>OSS The CJUG became involved in the Adopt-a-JSR program in 2014, when we officially adopted JSR 366, the Java Platform, Enterprise Edition 8 Umbrella specification. The Adopt-a-JSR program is led by the Java Community Process (JCP), with a goal of getting JUGs more involved with the Java specifications process. During our tenure as Adopt-a-JSR participants, we have held a number of sessions in person and online, in an effort to help foster each of the different JSRs that came together to comprise Java EE 8 and Java SE 9.</description></item><item><title>Sponsors</title><link>https://cjug.org/sponsors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cjug.org/sponsors/</guid><description>Current Sponsors Be a Sponsor Sponsorship Type Benefits Cost Gold 1 year logo on Marketing Material for all CJUG Events (CJUG4Kids, Polyglot, Meetups); First dibs on venue (with a non-sponsored speaker) All Silver benefits $3000 (only 2 of these available) Silver Logo on web properties (website, Meetup page); Logo on meetup slides $1500 Friends of Polyglot Logo on Polyglot Party as a sponsor $1000 Friends of CJUG4Kids Logo on CJUG4Kids events $1000 Conference Scholarship Logo and Thank You in CJUG newsletter on Scholarship Award Announcement $1000</description></item></channel></rss>